[Music]
you can use the other
once you come during the fighting
[Music]
where is there no yet that's about the
limit
' you space pasta feed DCI and then so
it's a little bit unusual word even word
[Music]
without there
in the wrong way
[Music]
there was someone straight
with
[Music]
so business
then you have to put in
[Music]
so
[Laughter]
[Music]
comes out roach
you can J this llama says that's the
llama is also some problem
[Music]
rhasta so Monica Quan
my parents
[Music]
if you hang out with people in the world
any person with
[Music]
but find the best ones so close you
learn they're significant not like some
people really like to overeat this idea
of a good dinner is coca-cola and a
Snickers bar hard for me to walk here
because I have to walk by the Snickers
bars
[Music]
in the king he was in the kingdom
everyone else telling you
[Music]
it's very hard
me
when you Protective Services and he said
don't forget the famous
[Music]
the first
okay there's a story here I told you
[Music]
he said
it means
[Music]
okay